autoclipping.com 2019-04-17

# Privacy policy

**AutoClipping Privacy Policy**

AutoClipping.com (hereinafter, “We,” “Us,” and “Our”) respects your privacy and has instituted this Privacy Policy to protect you (hereinafter “You” and “Your”) in Your capacity as a user of the site AutoClipping.com (hereinafter, the “Site”). Please read on to learn how We collect and use information obtained from the Site. If You have any questions about Our Privacy Policy or the Terms and Conditions, feel free to contact Us at support@autoclipping.com.

By Your access to and use of the Site, You agree to Our processing, storing and using certain information in accordance with the principles set out in this Privacy Policy. We will limit the collection and use of Your information to a minimum. We will only collect such information as is required to help You use the Site or keeping You informed about the services offered by Us or Our affiliates. The information You provide may also be used for analytical and statistical purposes, as specified herein.

**YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Personally identifying information is any information that can be used to identify and contact you, including your e-mail address, full name, or telephone number (what We call your “Personal Information”). When You register to use the Site, We ask for Your Personal Information.

**SECURITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We take reasonable, industry standard steps to safeguard the security and confidentiality of any information You provide to Us, including Your Personal Information. However, You agree that no matter what measures We take, it is technically impossible for Us to guarantee the security of any information You disclose online. You accept the inherent security implications of providing information over the internet and will not hold Us responsible for any breach of security or disclosure of information unless we have been negligent. Any password and user name allocated to You by Us must be kept secret and must not be disclosed to anyone, unless We have given You our prior written permission.

We will always maintain control over the confidentiality of your information. If you have consented or have provided us with your email address, we may periodically send you details of products and services which we offer. You may opt out of receiving these at any time by ticking the ‘opt out’ box provided in the promotional email message.

**DISCLOSURE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We will not sell, share, transfer, or otherwise disclose Your Personal Information to another party, except for as specified in the following cases:

  * Where We have previously informed You of such a transfer through disclosures or agreement, and We have Your authority to do so;
  * Where We are required by law to disclose Your Personal Information;
  * Where AutoClipping.com is sold, or substantially all of its assets are sold to another entity, We may disclose your Personal Information to the successor entity; and
  * Where such disclosure is, in Our sole discretion, necessary to protect the wellbeing of any third party.

**OUR USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

When you access the Site, Our server automatically collects certain information that is not personally identifiable, such as your IP address, pages viewed, and length of time spent on the Site. We collect and use this information, in the aggregate only, to diagnose problems with our server, to improve Our site, and to provide content of interest to You. We may also give affiliates and partners access to aggregate data about Our users and their use of the Site during user sessions. The information we share will not include Personal Information.

In order to provide you with thorough and personalized service, We may use “cookies” to keep and occasionally track information about You. A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. We sometimes use cookies to track information for Our users’ convenience and to understand our customers better. The cookies that are gathered by Us are only used by Us. At no time do We share information from cookies with third parties.

**LINKS TO OTHER SITES**

Please note that You could be directed to another site while using the Site. When You link to another site, You should review their privacy policy, as it may be different from Our Privacy Policy. Such sites may send their own cookies to users and otherwise collect data or solicit personal information. We are not responsible, and shall not be liable, for the privacy practices of linked sites or any use such sites may make of any information collected from You. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by the Site.

**USE OF IMAGES SENT TO US FOR AVAILING OUR SERVICES**

The Site provides services to remove backgrounds of images uploaded by customers. We will not use images sent for private or commercial use without Your prior consent. When processed, the images will be available at a public internet location, the URL of which will not be published. As this location is public (and therefore potentially available to any internet-connected device), We urge you to use discretion in uploading images that may be sensitive to You or to third parties. Under no circumstances shall We be liable for unauthorized transmission of images that do not belong to You.

**CHANGING THE INFORMATION WE HOLD ABOUT YOU**

If you would like to change the registration information we hold about you from our registration database, you may do so by sending an email message to: info@autoclipping.com.
